maxwellrender.com 2013-04-01

# Maxwell Render :: Privacy Policy

Next Limit Technologies - PRIVACY POLICY

**Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.   We at Next Limit take privacy very seriously.  We are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal data collected at our internet web sites.  **

This policy applies to all Next Limit´s internet web sites including, but not limited to, [www.nextlimit.com](http://www.nextlimit.com/), [www.realflow.com](http://www.realflow.com/), [www.maxwellrender.com](http://www.maxwellrender.com/) and [www.xflow-cfd.com](http://www.xflow-cfd.com/). 

General and Non-identifiable Information  

In general anyone can visit our web sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Our web servers will collect non-identifiable information from visits to our web sites, for example the IP address of your computer, number of visits to the web sites, time spent on the site, pages and images viewed, and content downloaded from our web sites. We may use a third party organisation to collect and analyse this data. This information is anonymous and not linked to any personally identifiable information, and is used to measure the use of our web sites and help improve the web sites to fit the needs of visitors. 

Collection of Personal Information

To access certain parts of our web sites, and/or to complete certain transactions such as downloading our software or entering a survey or contest, you may be asked to register and provide more specific information about yourself such as name and email address. Supplying such information is optional, but you may be unable to complete certain transactions or you may be prevented from accessing certain services without providing such information. 

We collect contact information at trade shows and events, we invite you to download free software from our website in return for your contact information and we run contests or surveys where we require participants to provide information at registration. And we collect personal information at the point of sale of our products. 

We request this information because we believe it is important to understand who our customers and prospects are, and how to contact them with relevant product information. .

Use of Personal Information

In general the personal information you provide us will be used to provide you with a variety of information and services to help you get the most from our products and services, to improve our product offerings and support your use of our web sites. 

Next Limit may use the personal information you provide us for a variety of purposes including registration and marketing. We may use the information to inform you of product updates and upgrades, product news, special offers, contests, and other Next Limit products and services that may be of interest to you. 

When you are a customer of Next Limit products or services, we may use your information to contact you about normal customer relation / customer service purposes, for example to address a question relating to an order or to enquire about your intention to upgrade your software. 

Authorised Resellers of our software are an important sales channel and for many customers provide support and training. We may share personal contact information with a reseller within your territory.

If you do not wish to receive information by email about additional Next Limit products or services, or those of partners and other companies including resellers, you may opt out when you provide your personal information and/or each time you receive such messages. You may also write to salesdesk@nextlimit.com clearly indicating who you are and the email address which corresponds to our records and which you want removed from receiving emails. Please note that due to the lead times involved, you may receive emails for a period of time after your opt-out notification.

Next Limit may disclose personal information if required by law or if Next Limit believes in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a legal process or protect Next Limit, our customers or the public. 

Information Security

All personal information is stored on secure servers and uses appropriate secure transport protocols including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, and unauthorised access or disclosure.

No data transmission over the internet is 100% secure, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Next Limit reserves the right to change out Privacy policy from time to time, and in its sole discretion. It is your responsibility to regularly check our web sites for amendments to this policy.
